Guide to the Cooperative Extension Service Publications 1967-1986
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Cooperative Extension Service Publications
1967-1986
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 244
Washington State University. Cooperative Extension.
5 Linear feet of shelf space 5 boxes
The Washington State University Cooperative Extension Service was founded in 1913. The collection consists of Cooperative Extension Service records relating to publications and new releases relating to agricultural issues.
The Washington State University Cooperative Extension Service was founded in 1913. Originally known as the Agricultural Extension Service, it took the current name to reflect the cooperative nature of this service, which is funded by federal state and local agencies. The state level organization of the service is operated by WSU in its capacity as the land-grant college for the state of Washington.
The collection consists of Cooperative Extension Service records relating to publications and new releases relating to agricultural issues.
During the 2011 reprocessing subjects were reordered alphabetically. Within each subject the existing order was retained, which was primarily by date.
This collection is open and available for research use.
This collection was apparently acquired some time prior to 1984, and recorded as UA 1983-13. As items in the collections date to the end of 1986, presumably further items were added at an undetermined date. It is unclear when and how the collection was initially processed, as no guide was apparently created, but it was most likely done during the summer of 2000.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. Cooperative Extension.
Agricultural extension work -- Washington (State)
Washington (State); Agriculture
- Agent Releases Index, 1970 - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agent Releases. Subjects A - H, 1970 - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agent Releases. Subjects I - W, 1970 - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agent Releases Index, 1973 [1] (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Agent Releases Index, 1973 [2] (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agent Releases. Subjects A - H, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Agent Releases. Subjects I - Y, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Agent Releases. Subjects A - F, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Agent Releases. Subjects H - Y, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Agent Releases Index, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Agent Releases Index, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Agent Releases Index, 1977 - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Agent Releases. Subjects A - W, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Agent Releases. Subjects A - S, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Agline Releases, June, 1982 - June, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Agline Releases, July, 1983 - May, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Agline Releases, June, 1984 - December, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Agline Releases, January, 1985 - June, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Agline Releases, August - December, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- CA Newsletter, 1967 - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CA Newsletter, 1970 - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- College of Agriculture and Home Economics. Annual Awards Banquet, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Consumergram, 1976 - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Consumer Cues Questions. Subject C - S, 1975 - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Consumer Cue Questions. Subjects C - S, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Consumer Cues Questions, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Consumer Questions. Subjects C - S, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Consumer Questions. Subjects C - S, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Consumer Questions. Answered, 1977 - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Consumer Questions. Answered, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Consumer Questions. Answered, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Consumer Questions. Answered, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Consumer Reporter Index, 1975 - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Consumer Reporter Index, 1977 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Consumer Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Consumer Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Cues for News, 1974 - 1976; August, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Dollar Stretcher, 1971 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Family Living Press January, 1982 - June, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 39-40)
- Family Living Press, July, 1983 - June, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Family Living Press, July, 1984 - December, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Family Living Press, January - June, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Farm Home Calendar, 1977 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Farm Home Calendar, 1980 - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Farm and Home Calendar, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Farm and Home Calendar, January - June, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Farm Reporter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Farm Reporter, January - July 21, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Farm Reporter, July 21 - December, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Farm Reporter, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Food Facts, 1979 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Idea Thing Handout Index. Programs 501 - 539, 1977 - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Idea Thing Handouts. Programs 703 - 726, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Information for Young Family Newsletter, 1977 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Just for You. English and Spanish Texts, September, 1972 - April, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- News Releases Index, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- News Releases. Subjects A - 4H, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- News Releases. Subjects Hort. - W, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- News Releases Index, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- News Releases. Subjects A - H, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- News Releases. Subjects I - W, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- News Releases Index, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- News Releases. Subjects A - H, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- News Releases. Subjects I - W, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- News Releases Index, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- News Releases. Subjects A - Ent., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- News Releases. Subjects Env. - Y, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- News Releases. Subjects Adm. - Arg, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- News Releases. Subjects Animal science - Fruit Trees, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- News Releases. Subjects Food Science - Resident Instruction, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- News Releases. Subjects Admin. - Animal Science, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- News Releases. Subjects Entomology - Misc., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- News Releases. Subjects Plant Pathology - Rural Soc., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- News Releases. Subjects Admin - 4H, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- News Releases. Subjects Horticulture - Rural Sociology, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- News Releases, January - March, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- News Releases, April - June, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- News Releases, July - December, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- News Releases, January - March, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- News Releases, April - June, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- News Releases, July - September, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- News Releases, October - December, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- News Releases, January - March, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- News Releases, April - June, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- News Releases, July - September, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- News Releases, October - December, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Northwest Reporter, July - December, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Northwest Reporter, January - June, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- On the Home Front, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 90)
- On the Home Front, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Pest Report, 1978 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Pest Report, 1980 - 1981 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Pocketer, 1976 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Press Pack. Index, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Press Pack. Subjects A - W, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Press Packet, 1980 - 1983 (Box 5, Folder 95)
- Puyallup News Releases, 1977 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Puyallup News Releases, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 97)
- Puyallup News Releases, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 98)
- Puyallup News Releases, 1984 - 1985 (Box 5, Folder 99)
- Puyallup Press Releases, 1981 - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Radio Script. Subjects A - M, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 101)
- Radio Scripts. Subjects C - S, 1977 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 102)
- Thought for Food, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 103)
- Thought for Food, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 104)
- Thought for Food, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 105)
- Thought for Food, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 106)